PARADA PREEPREAM

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Ruby on rails
JavaScript
Node.js
HTML
CSS
React
Bootstrap
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop

PERSONAL SKILLS

Color theoryConcept Sketch up Auto cad 3D max

Hobbies

Reading Painting Hiking Meditation

CONTACT

P: 970-817-1904 E: Paradafaii28@gmail.com

SOCIAL

fb:www.facebook.com/parada.faii

IG:@iamalicceeee

Twiiter: @ParadaRichards1

Github: Paradafaii28

ABOUT

My name is Parada (Alice) Richardson. I am originally from Thailand, and I have lived in the USA for almost 4 years now. My move to America has been a dream come true. I earned a degree with a major in interior design, and a minor in architecture. I love the opportunity to be creative and work to solve problems. Becoming a software developer is the next chapter in my life, and I very interested and passionate to be able to learn this new skill

Creative and enthusiastic. Very personable, with a talent for developing sold client relationships. Outstanding work ethic with a dedication to exceeding expectation. Willingness to learn and eager to always improve upon my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERIOR DESIGNER AT IDLM

Dec Aug 2013 – Dec 2013 in Thailand

INTERIOR DESIGNER AT AI ARCHITECTURE AND DESIGN
Jan 2015 – July 2015 Bangkok,
CAFÉ DE BANGKOK
April 2017 to present
COMFORT DENTAL
Nov 207 – April 2018Davis
FAMILY DENTAL
April 2018 – present

EDUCATION

BANGKOK UNIVERSITY, BANGKOK,THAILAND BACHELOR'S DEGREE February 2011 – April 2014 AMERICAN SCHOOL OF DENTAL ASSISTING, FORT COLLINS, CO DENTAL ASSISTANT (EDDA) June 2017 – October 2017 FLATIRON SCHOOL, DENVER, CO SOFTWARE DEVELOPER January 2020 – Present